have already been imprisoned Yes, for a
сидели уже
long time,
Да долго
how many half of my life I have been imprisoned for about 19
сколько полжизни просидел что зако 19
years
лет
Hello Hello, I am from the city of
Здравствуйте Здравствуйте я из города
Me Where did you
ме Вы
understand from Russia that this is a
откуда с России понял да это
national costume - embroidered shirt and can you
национальный костюм вышиванка а какие в
tell me what national costumes are in Russia? I am
России национальные костюмы подскажете я
also interested in
тоже интересуюсь
Yes, we have many nationalities,
Да у нас много национальностей у
everyone like the Russians What is the national
каждо как у русских Какой национальный
costume  Yes, a simple shirt, a
костюм Да простая рубаха что рубаха
simple shirt, that is, it’s interesting that the Udmurts have an
простая то есть интересно удмурта
embroidered shirt, the Erzas have an embroidered shirt, the
вышитая рубаха там у эрз вышитая рубаха
Russians also have a simple shirt, Kantik Well, it’s
простая руских тоже есть Кантик Ну
roughly similar to NTI, I
примерно похож на НТИ
understand Red Ghana shirt, I
понял Красная Гана рубаха
understand about the World Cup in general
понял о ЧМ
Yes, I just decided to
обща Да просто я решил
talk to the
пообщаться с братьями
Slavic brothers, mostly people have a negative
славянами в основном люди негативно
attitude  to the Russian Federation Well, yes,
относятся к Российской Федерации Ну да
because, well, you’re not Slavs,
потому что ну вы же не славяне у вас там
we’re all Slavs, Poles. It’s just that Russia
все мы славяне поляки свя просто Россия
looks after Ukraine.
смотрите вот за Украину свя
In short, it’s not clear. Well, it turns out that you’re fighting against the
короче непонятно Ну получается вы против
Slavs.
славян
Well, Russia is killing the Slavs in
воюете Ну да Россия убивает славян в
Ukraine. Russia is also a SV, so not Russia.
Украине Россия тоже СВ так не Россия Там
you said there are different peoples there, they are not
все вы сказали там разные народы там не
Slavs
славяне
Yes, don’t knock something there, there are
Да не стукай там чтото стукае
many other nationalities living on our territory, that’s not correct. There are many
у нас на нашей территории живёт много
nationalities
других национальностей
living on your territory.
неправильно не На вашей территории живёт
And you live on the
много национальностей А Вы живёте на
territory of different nationalities, that’s
территории разных национальностей вот
right. Yes, that’s who you think is race. I
правильно Да это Кто вам такое раска Я
said you  say that
сказал вы говорите что На вашей
different nationalities live on your territory,
территории живут разные национальности
it’s the other way around, it’s you living on their
это наоборот это Вы живёте на ихней
territory, they lived from time immemorial.
территории они жили и спокон веков
They didn’t live there; the Tatars didn’t live; the
Там они там не жили кто татары не жили
Bashkort didn’t live; the Udmurts didn’t live;
башкорт Не жили удмурты Не жили А где
well, the Bashkirs are the Udmurts, this whole thing is
хорошо башкиры удмурты вот эта вся это
generally a Fino-Ugric nation, if the
вообще фино угорская нация если что
Bashkor are the Fino-Ugric so the Fino-Ugric
башкор тю фино угорская так фино угор
they lived in these places from
они жили на этих местах испокон
time immemorial. Well, so what, it’s you who live on their
веков Ну и что так это вы на ихней
territory and not them on
территории живёте а не они на
yours no yes their territory was
вашей нет да ихняя территория была
conquered in the Middle Ages  Well, you live
завоёвана Средние века Ну вот вы живёте
on their
на ихней
territory, just like your Kiev Rych
территории так же как ваша Киевская рыч
was conquered, also look, you live
была завоёвана тоже смотри вы живёте да
on the territory of the Udmurts and various other
на территории удмуртов и разных других
Finno-Ugric peoples. Well, you are like
фино угорских народов Ну типа вы
tenants, so to
квартиранты можно так
speak. No, the indigenous people are not like the
сказать Нет коренные жите нет как
indigenous Slavs there from Radya. Although, what if
коренные там славян от Радя Хотя А если
you  not Slavs, I understood that is, you are a Finno-
вы не славяне я понял то есть вы фино
Ugric people Merya tribe Merya which
угорский народ меря племя меря которое
later adopted one of the Slavic dialects
потом приняла один из славянских наречий
And now you called yourself Russian That
Да и сейчас назвали себя русскими То
is, you are a Naugrian people, I understood a
есть вы фи наугорский народ я понял
conglomerate of Finno-Ugric different tribes
конгломерат фино угорских разных племён
not only Well, yes Well, you are sorties and
не только Ну да Ну вот вы вы вылеты и
Finns
фино
Ugric, I’m just an anthropologist You’re not, you’re fino, I’m
угр я просто антрополог Вы нет Вы фино я
anthropological, I have 18 years of experience, in 2 years there
антропо у меня 18 лет стажа через 2 года
will be two I’m a candidate of sciences, by the way, I
будет два я кандидат наук кстати скоро
’ll soon defend my doctorate in 2 years, I
докторскую через 2 года буду защищать
just wanted to have twenty years of experience,
как раз хотел к двадцатилетнего стажу
so you have an anthropological type Yes,
так вот у вас антропологический тип Да
Balto Ugric is called
Балто угорский называется
uh, classic
ээ классическая
dolichocephaly  with elements of hydrocephalus,
долихоцефалия с элементами гидроцефалии
there is, well, show me without glasses, I’ll
вот есть а ну Покажите без очков на
look at your eyes. Well, take off your glasses and get a little closer
глаза гляну ваши Ну снимите очки и ближе
to the camera. Well, so that my pupils are like that, a
чуть к камере Ну чтобы я зрачки так
shell. Yes, there is such a thing, there is a small
оболочка Да есть такое есть небольшая
Slavic admixture, apparently the grandfather was
примесь Славянская видно дед был
a Slav, and one of the grandfathers was a
славянином да один из дедов был
great-grandmother, in general, a Don Cossack.  it
прабабушка вообще Донская Казачка Вот
means from the great-grandmother from the great-grandmother
вот значит от прабабушки от прабабушки
Rainbow this and the rest is the
Радужная это а остальное так эпикантус
Turkic epicanthus and you can turn sideways
тюркский есть а боком можете повернуться
profile Yes, look, you have a
профиль Да вот смотрите у вас тут
rear passage here, you can look at
переход задний всё можете смотреть на
me, here is the transition hole Yes,
меня вот тут ямка перехода Да
characteristic of the Finno-Ugric peoples
характерная для ээ фино угорских народов
who lived in the Aki and Volga interfluve
э которые жили в Междуречье Аки и Волги
from the seventh to the 13th century here, the fact is
с седьмого по 13 век вот э Дело в том
that there, just when fossil
что там как раз когда и ископаемые
burials are found, it is also among the
захоронения так находят именно тоже у
Slavs that there is a slightly different transition here.
славян немножко другой тут переход
Slavic Germanic type of transition, uh,
Славянский германский тип перехода ээ
in the back of the cranium, it has a slightly
задне черепной коробки он немножко имеет
different concavity, here you have it, that
другую вогнутость вот у вас как раз то
is, you are an autochthon  on this territory That
есть вы автохтон на этой территории То
is, there is no doubt about it Yes, I said that you
есть тут сомнений нет Да я сказал что вы
live on their land No, this is
живёте на ихней зем Нет это
really your Land because your
действительно ваша Земля потому что ваш
phenotype coincides with those fossil
фенотип совпадает с теми ископаемыми
anthropological types that lived
антропологическим типами которые жили
there, the Finno-Ugric peoples in the 6th century And so
там фино угорские народы в VI веке И так
on, yes That is, in principle Just  you are
дальше да То есть в принципе Просто вы
now speaking one of the
сейчас разговариваете на одном из
Slavic dialects like
славянских наречий типа
yes, I actually grew up here and speak the
да я вообще-то вырос здесь и говорю на
language of the country in which I grew up Dada
языке страны в которой я вырос Дада
Well, look Buryak Koto Gory in the language but I
Ну смотрите буряк кото гор на языке но
don’t speak the language of the part of the country in
не говорю на языке той части страны в
which I am present now because it’s
которой я присутствую сейчас потому что
different here  language is present
здесь другой язык есть присутствует
understood From the side I understand And look Or you
понял Со стороны понял А смотрите А
can also turn around, that’s interesting I
можете ещё развернуться вот интересно Я
want to look in some Finno-
хочу посмотреть в некоторых фино
Ugric captivity they are differentiated by the
угорских плена они дифференцируются по
cut of the shoulders, you can turn the
разрезу плечей можете повернуться
shoulder composition to show
плечевой состав показать
me like this and Hands to the side so that well, how the
мне так а Руки в сторону чтобы ну как
arm span was to straighten the shoulders Yes, I
размах рук был чтобы расправить плечи Да
see  everything can be turned Yes, yes,
вижу всё можно поворачиваться Да есть
yes, yes, yes, that is, in principle, yes, the Finno-
Угу да То есть в принципе да фино
Ugric type is confirmed, it is, oh,
угорский тип подтверждается это есть о
and the length, by the way, your fingers are
а длина кстати пальцы у вас пальцы
short or long, you can show
Короткие или длинные можете показать
the long ones, Well, medium ones with some length, not not
длинные Ну средние с как-то дли не не
close to the camera so that I can compare them with your face
близко к камере чтобы я вот с лицом
put long, long fingers near your face,
сравнил вот возле лица поставьте длинные
yes, long fingers, yes, that
длинные пальцы да длинные пальцы да то
is,
есть есть
Yes, don’t show that on your legs, but they are
Да такое на ногах не показывайте но на
also long on your legs. As I understand it, yes,
ногах тоже длинные Я так понимаю да
elongated. Everything is there, it’s
удлинённые Всё всё есть есть это
called fromo podia, fromo podia,
называется фрого подия фрого подия
uh, it’s a term in Latin. Yes, it’s
ээ она это термин по латыни Да оно
common among people.  some Baltic
распространено у балтийских некоторых
peoples Yes, among the Finno-Ugric peoples and among the
народов Да у фино угорских народов и у
peoples of the north. The fact is that in the
народов севера Есть дело в том что они в
process of evolution they lived in more severe
процессе эволюции жили в более суровых
conditions there, winter Snow and
условиях там зима Снег да
formed in a warm climate, they
формировались в Тёплом климате они еду
got food more easily, picked from a tree all
добывали проще сорвал с дерева круглый
year round, yes they have short fingers, yes  it
год да у них короткие пальцы да у вас
turns out that your ancestors are
получается то есть ваши предки они те
short-fingered, they died out
коротко пальцевые они вымирали потому
because they couldn’t get food for themselves from under
что не могли добыть себе еду из-под
the Cover of Snow, the hatchling is
Покрова снега вылуп вот
like this. Therefore, these are mostly
такое Поэтому вот это ноп основном
long fingers, I first defined it like that
длинные пальцы я вот сначала так определ
then and then I assumed that yes, you have
потом и предположил что да у вас пальцы
long fingers, you see Yes  there is such a thing Yes,
длинные видите Да есть такое Да
that is, you think that the Slavs
вот то есть вы считаете что славяне
are only in the western part of Europe
только находятся в западной части Европы
no no Eastern too, for example
нет нет Восточный тоже вот например
Ukraine Belarus Slavs
Украина Белорусь славяне
Yes Ukraine Belarus is the Slavs and
Да Украина Беларусь - это славяне а
Russia is no longer a NE in Russia look
Россия - это уже не СВ в России смотрите
in Russia there is an inclusion The thing is that
в России есть вкрапление Дело в том что
there is  this is
есть такая
now not only anthropological, I am an anthropologist, yes,
сейчас не только антропо я антрополог да
I
я
look at the characteristics physiologically, there are also
физиологически смотрю характеристики ещё
geneticists who study haplogroups in
есть генетики исследует гаплогруппы в
DNA such And here is the haplogroup R1 R1 R1 A1,
ДНК такие И вот гаплогруппа R1 R1 R1 А1
it is widespread and the largest
она распространена э самая большая
concentration is in the territory of Ukraine and
концентрация на территории Украины и
Poland, Belarus and related ones, in
Польши Белоруси и сопутствующих есть в
Russia there is an inclusion of the pl group R1 A1 there is
России вкрапление пл группы R1 А1 есть
in parts of the Belgorod region of
на части Белгородской области
Voronezh and in the Kuban, uh,
Воронежской и на кубане ээ учёные
genetic scientists say that this is due to the fact
генетики и говорят что это связано с тем
that these were ethnic territories
что это были этнические территории
that were under the control of Kievan
которые были под контрольны Киевской
Rus and were populated, for example, the Belgorod region, it
Руси и заселялись например белгородчина
was populated by Ukrainians, that is,
она была Заселена украинцами да то есть
before Khrushchev took it to Russia,
до того как Хрущёв забрал её в Россию
so  there they lived there and they even say
так то есть там жили они и говорят даже
they’re ekat gaka Yes, Ukrainians were also resettled in the Kuban
они экат гака Да на кубане тоже были
there are in between the
переселены украинцы есть вот в между реч
Aki and Volga rivers there the Slavic component is
Аки и Волги там уже Славянский компонент
not present genetic de is
не присутствует генетический де в том
that now it’s all very simple but
что это сейчас всё очень просто да вот
they take samples from thousands of people so
берут пробы у тысячи людей так
medical  do an analysis and look at
медицинские делают анализ и смотрят
what percentage so uh The further it goes
Какой процент так вот э Чем дальше идёт
into the Aki-Volga interfluve and the
в Междуречье Аки и Волги да тем падает
Slavic component falls and the Finno-
именно Славянский и повышается фино
Ugric component rises there is such a thing that is uh
угорский компонент есть такое то есть э
The thing is that here a process took place here
Дело в том что тут Тут прошёл процесс ээ
uh let’s say like the Bulgarians Bulgarians are
ээ скажем как вот у Болгар Болгары они
Turks  but when they came to the Balkans, they
тюрки но они когда пришли на Балканы они
didn’t take the Balkans to Bulgaria, they took the
взяли не на Балканы в Болгарию они взяли
Slavic language, but the Bulgarians have a
славянский язык вот у Болгар язык
Slavic language, but they are Turks, they come from the
Славянский но они тюрки они родом из
Volga region, too, that’s where Bulgaria
Поволжья тоже вот оттуда воя Булгария
was from, and so on and so on and you get it,
была И так дальше так и у вас получается
so
вот
you are Fino coals, yes, but they took it  Slavic language
вы фино угли да Но взяли славянский язык
just like the Buryats, now the Buryats are
так же как буряты вот сейчас буряты
now losing their Buryat language and
сейчас утрачивают свой бурятский язык и
are starting to speak Russian, they are Buryats,
начинают говорить по-русски они буряты
but in a generation or two they will all
но через поколение два они уже все будут
speak Russian. But they remain
говорить по-русски Вот Но а остаются
Buryats; there is no ethnic difference there
бурятами не есть там этническая всё
anyway. And look at you  where are your
равно фор А вас смотрите у вас у вас
parents from? From which
родители откуда С каких вот бабушки
grandparents from which regions of Russia? I’m
дедушки с каких регионов России Мне
interested in one Kuban Cossack,
интересно одна Кубанская Казачка
the rest. Well, look, that is, it’s
остальные Ну вот смотрите то есть вот
the great-grandmother of the Don Cossack, she
раз прабабушка Донская Казачка она
moved to the Far East, where my grandmother was born.
переехала на Дальний Восток там родилась
My grandfather is from the center of Russia, from the
моя бабушка Мой дед с центра России с
center, where exactly is this from?  important
центра откуда именно это важно центр
there is a different center Well, the center is just
разный есть Ну центр - это как раз вот
this Finno-Ugric that is, well Volga Volga
это фино угорская то есть ну Волга Волга
Volga yes And what is the Volga Because there is a
Волга да А какая Волга Потому что есть
Turkic Volga there is a Finno-Ugric What is the
тюркская Волга есть фино угорская Какая
average average Volga region which is
средняя средняя Волга кая область какая
closer to Tatarstan Kaza Tatarstan Well this is a
ближе к Татарстана каза Татарстан Ну это
Turkic component already  You
тюркский компонент уже у вас
may be present,
присутствует возможно
Chuvash, well, there are Chuvash nearby, Yes,
Чуваши ну рядом рядом вот Чуваши Да
Chuvash is next to Volga Bulgaria Yes,
Чуваши это на сле Волжская Булгария Да
yes there is such a thing, and the second child is from where I
да есть такое так а второй дет откуда
don’t know about the second one. Well, in short, the point is
так про второго не знаю Ну короче суть в
that they met there, that is, in the
том что они там познакомились то есть на
Far East, my mother was already born
Дальнем Востоке мать у меня уже родилась
there  that is, this is generally the region of
там то есть это вот вообще край
Russia The Sea of ​​​​Japan where I know the Sea of ​​Okhotsk,
России Японское море где Охотское знаю
yes Well, they are already The fact is that they
да Ну это уже они Дело в том что они уже
were already resettled there under the Soviet Union,
были переселены при Советском Союзе туда
that is, yes I am interested, as a
то есть да Меня интересует меня как
scientist, I am interested in the roots of the origin of the
учёного интересуют корни происхождения
clan, where it was formed over
рода где он формировался в течение
the centuries, that’s where it comes from  I came
столетий Вот откуда она приехала
directly to take my Dedan from And
непосредственно взять моего Дедан от А
so the distant roots are the Don Cossacks, I
так дальние корни это донские казаки
realized
понял
yes there is such a thing Yes, well, the Don
да есть такое Да ну донски
Cossacks in my life it seems like there is such a
каза у меня по жизни как бы идт такая
trend that I don’t really get along with the law
тенденция что я не особо лажу законом
for a long time,
у долго
how many half of my life
сколько полжизни
I spent 19 years 19 years And you are now 38
просидела 19 лет 19 лет А вам сейчас 38
so that  half your life to talk Well, yes And how many times
чтоб полжизни говорить Ну да А сколько у
have you had two And for
было две А за
what for
что за
theft So how did you get 19 for theft
кражи Так а как вы 19 намотали за кражу
and
и
robbery Well, that’s how the last
разбой Ну вот так вот последний
15 years is this murder no robbery in a
15 лет это это убийство нет разбой в
group Yes no single Well do
групповой Да нет одиноч та Ну разве у
you have a sanction for  Solitary robbery for 15 years,
вас санкция за разбой одиночные 15 лет
but when executed, yes, like, it
сую а при исполнении да типа
turns out without execution, just judge
получается без исполнения просто суди
Cool And
Прикольно А
where Well, they
где Ну так на
didn’t know in teaching that he was a Judge, they just didn’t
уча не знали что он Судья просто да не
intend to accidentally want a bomb to hit the
намерено случайно хотели бомба попали на
judge Well, the first victim I had
судью Да ну первый потерпевший у меня
was a
был полковник
police colonel You’re
милиции Вы
exactly the one  I was for a
именно ходка у меня была за
police lieutenant colonel, he was our
подполковника милиции он был нашей
roof, he made money, I took a pony for him in the apartment,
крышей зажил деньги я нему в кварти пони
I dili, in short, well, as an
я дили короче ну как
initiator, in general, he was there obshchkovsky,
инициатора вот в общем он там обща
in short, he understood, that is, it turns out that he was kind of
короче понял то есть получается он типа
protecting you, like Kid zero you, you
крышевал вас да типа Кида нул вас вы
decided to take yours from him  grandmas Yes, he
решили забрать у него свои бабки Да и он
and I were later imprisoned Yes, that’s how old you
и меня потом посадили Да это сколько вам
were 20 17 at that time I got out at 20 I
было 20 17 на тот момент вышел в 20
understood I understood So good
понял понял Так хорошо
And how old were you when you turned the judge
А во сколько лет вы судью стукнули
23 23 Well, yes, like, you spent 3 years And what are
23 23 Ну да типа посидели 3 года А что
you doing for these 3
вы эти 3
years And what are you  3 years from 20 to 23 What
года А что вы 3 года с 20 по 23 Чем
did you do? At first I worked, then I did
занимались сперва работал потом вот
all sorts of things, I
всяко занимался
understood. But you bombed the judge on the street
понял А вот судью вы бомбанули на улице
like, well, what did you take from
типа ну что вы забрали у
her? Yes, I didn’t take anything. I just
неё Да я ничего не не забрал Я просто
E. So wait, so this is not robbery. This is
Е Так подожди Так это же не разбой Это
different. Well, I have  there were robbery
другая Ну у меня там были разбойные
attacks and since the article for beating is
нападения и так как статья за избиение
much lighter than the article for
намного легче чем статья за разбойное
robbery, robbery goes from 8 to 12.
нападение разбойное нападение от 8 до 12
Wait, then again, if you beat
идёт Подождите то ещё раз если вы избили
her, then where did the robbery come from? this is
её да то откуда разбой взялся разбой это
when she was still there Well, they just said that
когда ещё она Ну просто там сказали что
I demanded the value  Although I didn’t
я требовал ценности Хотя я ничего не
demand anything, I just sort of got into a
требовал Я просто как бы ну вступил в
brawl. But how about I was just on the street of
потасовку А а как л просто на ули ре
some person or I can’t understand
какого-то человека или не могу понять
how it
как это
happened. There was a brawl, well, that is, there was
получилось Там была потасовка ну то есть
first a verbal brawl, then the
была сперва словесная потасовка потом
judge, he or
судья он или
she was a woman  So which
она это была женщина Так какая по
one just accidentally touched me, she
Какая просто случайно задел она там
started drinking me with an umbrella,
начала меня зонтиком пить
in short,
короче вс
the umbrella took me away And since I was wanted for
зонтик А так как я был в розыске за
robbery in the case of something else, wait stop stop stop stop
разбой при а то стопчик подожди стоп
stop I understood then when the
стоп стоп стоп стоп понял то вы когда
judge you were already wanted for robbery yes
судью вы уже были в розыске за разбой да
And when I was caught, she wrote a
И когда меня поймали она-то написала
statement when I was caught. That is, as
заявление когда меня поймали То есть как
if they understood who I was, that is, as
бы они ну поняли кто я такой то есть как
if from the description on the Armed Forces, she recognized me,
бы по описанию по ВС она меня опознала
like there from the photo that I am Now, now
типа там по фоту что я Вот вот вот уже
He’s on your wanted list
Он в розыске у
Let’s say  that he demanded valuables from me
вас Давайте скажем что он у меня тревал
and then also besides the fact that I
ценности а потом ещ Помимо того за что я
was wanted for robbery, all the other centuries there, they
был в розыске разбой все другие веки там
hanged me and couldn’t find the rest.
повесили натри а нашл оста не смог
In short, they gave me 15 years because
Короче мне дали 15 лет по то что я
I was not created for the rest because they were
за остальные я не создался пому что это
not mine  I denied them It’s not mine, but they
не мои я их отрицал Это не мои но там
just honestly said it for their own,
просто то за свои честно
that’s me, that is, her I
сказали вот это я то есть её Я
beat her, she didn’t have anything, I didn’t
избил у неё ничего не было я е не
demand anything from us So this situation came up, I
требовал ничего у нас Вот Вышла такая
beat her up, judge, there’s no use
избил жв судь сни проку
at all, so they gave me 15  years old, yes, I’m still saying from
вообще вот мне дали 15 лет да говорю ещё
above Natalie Listen and look,
сверху Натали Слушай а смотри а за
why were you wanted for robbery for what were you wanted
разбой ты за что за что тебя разыскивали
for robbery for What episode Well, that is, I
за разбой за Какой эпизод Ну то есть я
took valuables there, money there, phones
забирал там ценности деньги там телефоны
Well, it’s so simple That is, as if he didn’t beat
Ну так просто То есть как бы не бил
anyone, a threat, that is, Zdorov just
никого угроза то есть Здоров просто
threatened  people
пригрозил люди
are like that I even, that is, well, physical
таква Я даже то есть ну физического
harm I didn’t cause any physical harm for my actions,
физического вреда я не
that is, you
наносил то есть ты
honestly, that is, you understood, you
честно то есть понял ты честно
honestly nobly approached, that is, showed and
благородно подходил то есть показывал и
gave them back without beatings, yes Well, how
отдавали сами без побоев да Ну как
nobly I
благородно я
approached, said some kind  threats, that
подходил говорил какие-то там угрозы то
is, to life and health Yes, it
есть для жизни и здоровья Да
was demonstrated, that is, well, the bailiff
демонстрировал то есть ну пристав его
could put him in the throat or the bailiff there in the stomach, but he
может горлу или там к животу пристав но
didn’t cut well, but it was such that the
не резал хорошо а а было такое что
person was there. And if the person, for example,
человек там А если бы человек например
said No, I won’t give it or no. What would you
сказал Нет не дам или нет У меня что бы
do?  basically, if a person has
делал Ну в принципе если у человека
nothing, he leaves. And as you know, he
ничего нет он уходит А как ты знаешь он
says I have nothing, well,
говорит у меня ничего нет а ну хорошо
okay, so far it was like this, I checked how I
ладно пока так было я проверял как
checked, be
проверял
silent, I understood. And look, you sat for so long,
молчи понял А смотри ты ты столько сидел
like an article you have there, what
типа вроде статьи у тебя там какие
kind of thieves’ tattoos are there?  on
воровские такие типа есть наколки на
the body
теле
there is And where I didn’t see on the hands and what do they
есть А где я не видел на руках а что они
symbolize on the legs Well, that’s so, that
символизируют на ногах Ну это так то
is, as if it’s not prison, not prison,
есть как бы это не тюремные не тюремные
but I understood for myself for there is there is a
да для себя понял для есть есть
hemp leaf That is, before I
конопляный лист То есть раньше Я
was fond of
увлекался
And you you According to the prison hierarchy Who
А ты ты По тюремной иерархии Кем
was in the prison hierarchy a man a man
был по тюремной иерархии мужик мужик
would have understood not Blokov In short, I didn’t
понял бы не блокова Короче не блокова
understand Blokov yes because Stu Yes there are no such stars
понял да потому стю Да нету звёзд таких
Yes there is nothing like that I understood Okay
Да нет такого ничего нет понял Хорошо
let’s understand I’ll run further already Okay
давай понял побегу дальше уже О'кей
life has beaten you down Hold on
жизнь тебя потрепала Держись
Let’s write to my Telegram directly at once
Давай пиши на мий Telegram прямо зараз
VN axis
ось ВН а
Popik is more and more respectful YouTube
Попик це дуже и дуже важливо YouTube
driving us through the skarg Orcs into your ban
загоняя нас через скарг Орки в твый бан
and even more videos I don’t show people
и дуже багато вдео не показую людям
constantly I don’t show information about streams
вчасно не показуе информация про стрими
For this purpose, we need to
Тому для того щоб ми Мали оперативный
write an operational link in Mali right away and in the meantime, in
звязок пишиться прямо зараз а пок там в
telegrams okm video is also tsikava and
телеграми окм видео ще теж цикава и
korisna information and mi povinni z you
корисна информация и ми повинни з вами
trimati postiyny operative link
тримати постийний оперативный звязок
nezalezhno in that chi show you the process
незалежно в того чи покаже вам проце
YouTube Slava ukraini pidpishit
YouTube Слава украини пидпишить